Short for peanut butter and jelly one of the most classic American prisons in the Canon
花生酱和果冻的缩写，是美国佳能公司最经典的监狱之一
Does a peanut butter and jelly
请问花生酱和果冻
It was always like this sad seriously got on field trips
总是像这样的悲伤认真地实地考察
Bruce question on Jesus would you like looks like I've got a whole wheat bran and sprout
关于耶稣的布鲁斯问题，您希望我看起来像个麦麸和新芽吗？
Ok
好
This one reminds me of Childhood
这个让我想起了童年
I'm good good white bread
我是好白面包
The white bread is classed as if your parents are
白面包的分类就好像您的父母是
This looks really healthy
这看起来真的很健康
Crunchyroll premium
嘎吱嘎吱的溢价
I'm going to keep organic peanut butter
我要保留有机花生酱
Elvis is crunchy organic peanut butter
猫王是松脆的有机花生酱
Turn it all the quarters
把它全部转过来
Because you should always challenge yourself
因为你应该总是挑战自己
And I think it's like the great debate do you put peanut butter on both sides or just one
我认为这就像是一场伟大的辩论，是将花生酱放在两面还是一面
Such an American singer Ryan
这样的美国歌手瑞安
Even spread the fastest way
甚至以最快的方式传播
The thickness of a penny
一分钱的厚度
Strawberries
草莓
Great
大
Classic
经典
Grape jelly
葡萄果冻
Jabot in various parts of the sandwich
Jabot在三明治的各个部分
I like a swing
我喜欢秋千
The situation
情况
TV
电视
Flipping
翻转
Right down the middle
就在中间
Yeah I'm good
是的，我很好
Play some of the Dragon
玩一些龙
Google can you have to clean in triangles because the other way is just name
Google一下是否可以将三角形清理干净，因为另一种方法就是名称
Add scientifically proven that
加入科学证明
When does Harry make a pie in a nice sturdy white bread ok
哈利什么时候用坚固的白面包做馅饼好
Grape jelly
葡萄果冻
Created by
由...制作
I think I'm good for your vagina
我想我对你的有好处
50% out of 30% or more on the maximum side here of peanut butter and jelly song
30％以上的花生酱和果冻中有50％以上
You have to go all the way to the edges
你必须一直走到最边缘
Nothing worse than Peter Burns away everything stuck in the centre and a Fermanagh jelly
没有什么比彼得·伯恩斯更糟糕的了，他消除了卡在中间的所有东西和一个费马纳果冻
All the way to the edges using a spoon jelly tensei slime off of the night
晚上用汤匙果冻浓稠粘液一直到边缘
I know I do here
我知道我在这里
Turn together
一起转
A nice
一个不错的
Symbol diameter
符号直径
I want to see for the perfect girlfriend
我想找完美的女朋友
Enjoy your life
享受你的生活